[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This oldest house in The Bronx, build in 1748, is New York Citys first house museum, operated since 1897 as a public museum by The National Society of Colonial Dames in the State of New York.", "correct_answer": "Van Cortlandt House", "incorrect_answers": ["Valerian House", "Throgs Neck", "Fordam Arms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the year in which the worlds first nuclear power plant generating electricity for commercial use was officially connected to the Soviet power grid.", "correct_answer": "1954", "incorrect_answers": ["1956", "1953", "1955"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What effect does the consumption of figs produce on the human body?", "correct_answer": "It has a laxative effect.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "It lowers cholesterol.", "It reduces blood pressure."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although this actor never reached the fame of his ex-wife, he made a brilliant performance as the young policeman Tom Hansen in the 2004 movie Crash.", "correct_answer": "Ryan Phillipe", "incorrect_answers": ["Heath Ledger", "Brendan Frazer", "Bruce Kirby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jeff Spicoli, a character from Fast Times at Ridgemont High, portrayed by Sean Penn, wears what brand of sneakers?", "correct_answer": "Vans", "incorrect_answers": ["Adidas", "P. F. Flyers", "Converse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Genes are the units of heredity in living organisms. Variants of the same gene are known under what name?", "correct_answer": "alleles", "incorrect_answers": ["albumins", "nucleotides", "myosins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Angelina Jolie Voight was born on June 4, 1975 in this city.", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles, California, USA", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City, New York, USA", "Chicago, Illinois, USA", "Paris, France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country is the Gohongaze Starfish considered an edible delicacy?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Italy", "New Zealand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the film Dog Day Afternoon released?", "correct_answer": "1975", "incorrect_answers": ["1977", "1976", "1974"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who kills Evans in the western film 3:10 to Yuma?", "correct_answer": "Charlie Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["William Evans", "Mr. Butterfield", "Ben Wade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress starred opposite Sean Connery in the 1999 movie Entrapment?", "correct_answer": "Catherine Zeta-Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Salma Hayek", "All of these", "Angelina Jolie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Kurt Russel the actor that played the part of the U.S. head coach in the movie Miracle?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]